[
{
    "question": "What is the name of Rick's home dimension?",
    "choice1": "Dimension C-132",
    "choice2": "Dimension C-137",
    "choice3": "Dimension C-138",
    "choice4": "Dimension C-139",
    "answer": 2

},

{

    "question": "What is Morty's last name?",
    "choice1": "Sanchez",
    "choice2": "Smith",
    "choice3": "Johnson",
    "choice4": "Brown",
    "answer": 2
},

{
    "question": "What is the name of Morty's sister?",
    "choice1": "Summer",
    "choice2": "Jessica",
    "choice3": "Beth",
    "choice4": " Annie",
    "answer": 1
},

{
    "question": "Which character often says 'I'm Mr. Meeseeks, look at me!'?",
    "choice1": "Rick",
    "choice2": "Morty",
    "choice3": "Mr. Poopybutthole",
    "choice4": "Mr. Meeseeks",
    "answer": 4
},

{
    "question": "What is the name of Rick's spaceship?",
    "choice1": "The Spaceship",
    "choice2": "The Rickship",
    "choice3": "The Galaxy Cruiser",
    "choice4": "The U.S.S. Squanchy",
    "answer": 2
},
{
    "question": "Who is Morty's long-time crush?",
    "choice1": "Jessica",
    "choice2": "Summer",
    "choice3": "Tammy",
    "choice4": "Annie",
    "answer": 1
},
{
    "question": "What kind of creature is Squanchy?",
    "choice1": "Human",
   "choice2": "Birdperson",
    "choice3": "Cat-like alien",
    "choice4": "Cyborg",
    "answer": 3
},
{
    "question": "What is the name of Jerry's workplace?",
    "choice1": "The Office",
    "choice2": "The Galactic Federation",
    "choice3": "The Daycare",
    "choice4": "The Jerryboree",
    "answer": 4
},

{
    "question": "What is the name of Jerry's workplace?",
    "choice1": "The Office",
    "choice2": "The Galactic Federation",
    "choice3": "The Daycare",
    "choice4": "The Jerryboree",
    "answer2": 3
},
{
    "question": "What fruit does Rick turn himself into?",
    "choice1": "Apple",
    "choice2": "Orange",
    "choice3": "Pickle",
    "choice4": "Banana",
    "answer": 3
},
{
    "question": "Who is Rick's best friend from his past?",
    "choice1": " Birdperson",
    "choice2": "Squanchy",
    "choice3": "Morty",
    "choice4": "Jerry",
    "answer": 1
},

{
    "question": "What is the name of Rick's daughter?",
    "choice1": "Summer",
    "choice2": "Jessica",
    "choice3": "Beth",
    "choice4": "Tammy",
    "answer": 3
},
{
    "question": "What is the name of the episode where Rick and Morty go inside a homeless man's body?",
    "choice1": "Anatomy Park",
    "choice2": "The Ricks Must Be Crazy",
    "choice3": "Meeseeks and Destroy",
    "choice4": "Rick Potion #9",
    "answer": 1
},
{
    "question": "Who voices both Rick and Morty?",
    "choice1": "Dan Harmon",
    "choice2": "Chris Parnell",
    "choice3": "Justin Roiland",
    "choice4": " Spencer Grammer",
    "answer": 3
},
{
    "question": "What is the name of the Galactic Federation agent who hunts Rick? ",
    "choice1": "Tammy",
    "choice2": "Birdperson",
    "choice3": "Krombopulos Michael",
    "choice4": "Cornvelious Daniel",
    "answer": 4

},
{
    "question": "In which episode does Evil Morty first appear?",
    "choice1": " Close Rick-counters of the Rick Kind",
    "choice2": "Get Schwifty",
    "choice3": "The Wedding Squanchers",
    "choice4": " Rick Potion #9",
    "answer": 1

}

]